Yes, we get Superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls built between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
Despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through Believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
In the world we're in
United gently bringing
up Our thought again,
yeah We're the foolish ones we love
We'll carry on till we see the light
The sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core Is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The balls filled between us,
they will show So what we don't know
That's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers Superpowers Yes,
we've got superpowers
Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers Superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, with the superpowers.
I failed you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
If only I was stronger.
Let's leave the weeping
to our enemies, shall we?
We can't afford to lose control here.
Are you serious, Jean-May?
How could you say something
so cold at a time like this?
Just because you spent the least amount of
time with Pedro doesn't mean that you...
If we wallow in pity, then
even more lives may be lost.
The struggle we face is
one of life and death.
Pedro was well aware of the perils.
And was prepared to sacrifice
himself whenever necessary.
With his deed, he achieved victory.
Our enemies have suffered a great
many losses since you came here.
This certainly is an
unprecedented setback for them.
And together, your strength has
driven Big Mom into a corner!
Can't you hear Pedro's voice
echoing inside you, even now?
He's saying, onward!
luffy took notice
immediately that's why he
leapt into that duel
without a second thought
katakuri's bounty is worth over a billion
luffy is making a tremendous wager
we still have quite a way to go
we're still in toto land after all
stay sharp and alert Soon we'll
be pursued once more by Big Mom,
an unbeatable emperor.
And a fleet of enemy ships can close in
on us from any direction at any time.
So until we're able to escape the
territory where Big Mom reigns,
we can't let our guard drop for a second.
Listen to Pedro's wishes!
My deepest apologies, I
see now, I was out of line.
Nami tell us what to do right?
Sanji and his group will be
coming from Cacao Island.
So we'll want to meet up with them.
High winds will be coming soon—try
to ride it hard to starboard!
Sounds like a plan, Nami—we'll take
the tailwind, starboard heading west!
heading west It's the most direct route.
You can count on us.
I'll go replenish the
cola we just used up.
I'll keep a lookout.
Let's do it.
I'm in position.
Right.
I shall monitor the current.
enemies coming from six
o 'clock it's the same
ships from earlier and a
person no way seriously
what the heck but how what kind
of trick is this big mom is
walking across the water don't
be silly that's completely absurd
is it not water wait a sec
that's candy i think she's walking
on a giant moving candy blob
wait can she do something
like that oh no does that mean
there's only one person who has
that power it's him isn't it
you lickety miss me keep
it up candy sea slug Now,
where did our friend Zeus run off to?
Normally, this would
be his responsibility.
Carrying mom, that is.
They're catching up.
Not that I mind lending a hand.
I do have a score to settle, after all.
But Pedro's sacrifice!
How's this fair?
Lickety-losing my right arm ain't so bad.
I can just make a new one out of candy.
I do predict one minor
inconvenience, though.
Whenever I go to enjoy my
hot cup of afternoon tea,
I'll recall that damn mink.
as my lickety limb melts
away from the drink's heat.
Can you even imagine?
Nothing is more humiliating.
Indeed, what a heinous
crime he has committed.
Get your payback by any means necessary.
This rage of mine must be sated.
How shall I torment his friends?
Uh, hello?
What the heck?
Why did everyone else leave us?
So hungry.
I'm losing my strength.
I need fire.
Same.
I'd love some thunderclouds about now.
You don't say.
Lola from Thriller Bark, huh?
I didn't know she's a master of chocolate.
That's correct.
She was the minister of
chocolate running Cacao Island,
but she abandoned it when she ran away.
And ever since then, that
position has remained empty.
Gotcha, but why is that?
You ready for this one?
Everybody's favorite little candidate right
here keeps on rejecting the darn author.
Tell importing.
Look, I have my reasons.
The only person who should hold
that seat is my big sister, Lola.
I'm still kind of holding out hope
that she'll come back one day.
I can't really blame you.
What?
Are my eyes deceiving me?
They aren't! No way!
I believe that's my daughter up there!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Tang, she didn't hear me.
Bye, chiffon.
Oh, come on.
Would you please just climb out
of the coffin already, Pudding?
Not on your life.
I can't be seen wearing a wedding
dress sitting next to that man.
I don't want people to get
the wrong impression about me.
They'll assume we're
newlyweds heading out on
our honeymoon and we
simply can't have that.
What people you never know who's
prying eyes are watching dear sis.
Trust me on this one
Look, it just bothers me. Okay.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
Just don't fall off. Okay.
Hey, you shut your mouth
So sweet what a little prince.
He's worried about me
Who the hell do you think you are, huh?
I'll fall if I want to, so just mind
your own damn business, would ya?
I can see Cacao Island! Perfect.
The sooner we get cracking on
this cake, the better, I say.
Hey!
Are you even listening to
my callous rebuke, Sanji?
Yeah!
Check out this dumbass.
He broke his only way out of here.
Aw, you plain hero by sacrificing
yourself for your friends?
No, I'm gonna kick his ass!
Are you that stupid, kid?
You realize who you're fighting, right?
Don't you know General
Katakuri's bounties?
One billion, fifty-seven million?
He's the toughest of the
sweet three generals!
Huh?
I'm getting fire!
Hmm.
Not a bad technique.
Had to try it for myself.
But I think it's more
efficient to do it this way.
Show that bastard what you're made of!
Damn, man!
That is brutal!
You're tough.
But as I already told you,
there's nothing your powers can
do that mine can't do better.
You're inferior to me in
speed, power, and efficiency.
Way rubber loses to Mochi!
Shut up!
Get ready!
Gomp-gomp-gomp-gomp-gomp!
That's it.
Yeah, you wish!
Where did Straw Hat go?
That's the stuff.
General Katakuri's on a
whole different level.
You're testing your strength next.
Learn your lesson.
That is one big fist!
How come? Come!
Elephant!
Hide!
Redditories need a finger bone!
How was my elephant gun strong enough?
What a beautiful dress!
She's like an angel, isn't she?
The poor thing—her wedding
was completely ruined!
Is it wrong that I think
she's cute when she's sulking?
Because wow, it's the minister of?
of
Why is Lady Siobhan here?
Don't worry.
She's under control.
She never hurt me.
The rebellion wasn't her idea.
She was only involved in
this because of her husband.
It's gang Veggie's fault.
I'm sorry.
I told everyone that I was going to
force you to help me make the cake.
So we have to make it look believable.
No, it's fine.
I'm a traitor now, after all.
Nice one, Pudding.
You're a real pro.
Gosh, this really has been quite
the day for you, hasn't it?
Straw Hats invaded the
island, Page betrayed us.
Hate to say it, but I guess that wedding
of yours just wasn't meant to be.
It looks like that may
be for the best, though.
That Sanji seems like a real jackass.
All I can do is put that behind me.
You're so brave, an inspiration to us all.
I bet mama's furious about this isn't she?
Not just furious—she's
suffering from hunger pangs.
If
we don't satisfy her, she may
destroy the entire country!
Well,
that's worrisome to hear—so
is everything ready?
Yes, ma 'am!
We've called for 31 highly skilled
chefs to assist you on the job.
They were dispatched from whole cake
island an hour ago, so they should.
they should
Good day to you, Lady Pudding!
It's an honor.
As you may have surmised, we are the
31 head chefs of Whole Cake Island.
Or the WCI 31 for short.
Siobhan and I are going to bake
the only cake that can stop Mama.
The sooner we finish the
job, the more lives we save.
Please provide us your assistance.
Right.
I'm happy to report that we've
already begun preparations.
Lady Pudding suffered
more than anyone today.
Yet the only thing she's
thinking about is saving us.
Don't you worry.
We won't let Mama destroy
our country, I promise.
Even though our heart is aching,
she's turning all the sorrow into
a delicious life-sitting cake!
She's a baking angel of
salvation! Good luck!
You and Robin go inside, while
the crowd's focused on me.
Got it!
Everyone, please, listen up!
I have a favor to ask before I begin.
It's no exaggeration to say that our
cake will decide the fate of this nation.
Countless lives are on the
line, so we need to concentrate.
So please, until we're done, you
must stay out of the factory.
Don't even come close. Roger!
And no peeking.
I don't care who you are
or what you might need.
I want absolute privacy. Roger!
You won't hear a peek, Lady Patty!
You're so sweet. Thank you.
The whole island's cheering
for you! Good luck!
Good, now they won't see Sanji,
but dealing with the chefs will
be a little more complicated.
Chefs, please come inside one by one.
Beach, head chef of the first
kitchen, reporting for duty.
This should only take a sec
I'm just giving your memories a little...
edit
Could you let me down?
Okay, here you go
Bumpy ride?
No time to complain.
I drew a diagram of the wedding cake
on the way here to speed things up.
What?
You remember it?
Well, it's close enough.
That's crazy—the design is one
thing, but how do you know?
The ingredients without
ever tasting
it by
its scent.
This guy now—let's hurry up!
Every last second counts.
second counts
Y 'all's a pudding!
That chef outfit looks cute on you!
Don't tell me Lady Pudding is not already!
What a good husband.
Here to help. Huh? Me?
I edited the memories of the chefs,
so they don't know about
the whole wedding fiasco.
They think it went off without a hitch,
which would mean we're husband and wife now.
You know, happy as can be.
So this story is, the wedding cake was
ruined due to some unexpected weather.
Mama got angry, that's the same, so we
have to make the cake all over again.
Don't contradict their new memories, okay?
No problem.
The memories of when they made
the original cake are still fresh.
So with all of them here to help, we
should be able to reproduce it accurately.
Whoa!
Huh?
Who came up with this
diagram for the wedding cake?
And a recipe, too? That'd be me.
You sketched this out on
the way over here? Uh-huh.
Let me know if there's any mistakes.
Are you kidding me?
This recipe is immaculate all
the way down to the secret
ingredient Executive Chef Struzan's
been awake coming up with.
I heard you were skilled,
but I had no clue.
You are brilliant, sir.
Two newlywed chefs making
their own wedding cake.
Romantic, huh? Newlywed?
Quite the unusual situation, but you
might as well make the best of it.
Don't embarrass me.
I'm shy.
Sanji, your wife fainted!
His wife? Your wife!
Your wife! Your wife!
Sanji, sir!
Come help your wife!
Stop it!
You're killing her!
I really think gross!
I think gross! Get up!
What?
Now he's bossing me around?
Well, I like a man who
knows what he wants.
If he needs to wear the pants
in our relationship, then...
You know, mutual respect
is very important.
Hey, you talk down to me like that again,
and I swear I will skin your ass, Sanji.
So here's what I need.
Some non-homogenized milk,
sugar beets, and bananas.
Also black sesame seeds,
soy flour, and yogurt.
As much as you can get.
Yes, sir!
Listen up.
This job is life or death,
and it's a race against time.
Chiffon, get baking on that
giant chiffon cake immediately.
Pudding, you start tempering the chocolate
and make sure we have enough of it.
I'm setting the cook time at
two hours and forty minutes.
You weren't kidding when you
called this a race against time.
Once everything else is done,
I'll add my secret ingredient.
It'll bring boundless
joy to whoever tastes it.
It's the essence of true sweetness.
Wow, the essence of true sweetness, huh?
In about three hours,
we'll load the partially done cake on
a ship and depart from Cacao Island.
After it cools down a bit, we'll
decorate it while we're sailing.
Big Mom and the Sunny
should be heading our way,
and by the time they intercept us,
we'll have the greatest cake ever
made waiting for them. I see.
That sounds very efficient.
I don't know.
That pace is going to be murder.
I think it's impossible,
actually. Quiet, you!
We'll do it because the
alternative is dead!
In that case, we shall strive
to make the impossible possible!
All right.
Time to start baking.
They saved Lola and I'll save them.
I have to protect Sanji.
Just you wait.
This chiffon cake is going to be so
fluffy it'll bring the world to its knees!
This is the sweet chocolate of salvation.
Chocolate that will change fate itself.
Hang on just a little bit longer, Luffy.
I'll show them what I'm made of.
My chef spirit.
Katakuri, it's me.
Escaped from the jaws of death, Press.
By the skin of my tongue.
They really put on a sorry show.
Pedro licked the bucket.
Hey, Straw Hat, you saw it, didn't you?
He tried to sacrifice his worthless life
in some pathetic attempt to kill me,
but I'm still lickety living.
As you can see in other words, his
death was utterly lickety meaningless,
and you're going to die
in vain—just like he did.
So you just lickety lie there
and meet your maker quietly!
Why don't you and Straw Hats
underlings they escaped our
encirclement by launching
their damned ship into the sky?
Mama and I are chasing them down at this
very moment, taking a stroll on the waves.
They're trying their best to escape,
but we'll catch up, lickety split!
split
Amon's fleet will be here soon as well.
Hey, Barrel.
Oh, Katakuri.
You can rest when this is over.
Our soldiers can't go
anywhere if you're napping.
Right.
Straw Hat thought he was taking
a stand to save his crew.
Barrel, round up some of the soldiers
and set fire to Straw Hat's ship.
With pleasure.
Good news!
We found a mirror that
links to the ship's locker.
It's right here.
There's more where that came from, too!
A couple of flaming arrows straight
through the mirror room should do the job.
And while they're scrambling
to deal with the fire,
Mama will smash those rats
into itty-bitty pieces.
What the...
Hand over that mirror!
Don't lay a finger on my crew!
Are we having a one-on-one
duel or not, Straw Hat?
Suck on that!
Now, let's burn down that ship
before someone interrupts us again.
Roger!
I'll laugh if you miss, Choscar.
Is that a joke, Moscar?
Hurry!
Fire!
Stop it!
Stay away! Hey!
Same to you.
Those are my little siblings
you're trying to attack.
Leave them alone.
You're a piece.
Hey, it's me!
Nami, Chimpe, anyone!
Can you hear me?
Hey, can you hear me?
Is that Ruthie?
The mirror!
Hey, I'm here. What's wrong?
I need you to find all our mirrors. What?
Like in the bathroom or locker room? Huh?
Burn! Burn! Burn!
Ready for another one? Of course!
Waiting on you!
Burn! Burn!
Luffy!
What about the mirrors?
Break them all! To pieces!
Are you out of your mind?
Then how will you get back?
That was the whole plan!
Don't worry about me!
We'll get through this!
I'll work something out.
What's that?
I smell something.
Even though I don't have a nose, Yo-Ho-Ho.
The room's on fire!
What's wrong?
How did this happen?
What?
What?!
Flaming arrows from the mirror, cannon
shots from behind, one king after another!
If I had eyes in my sockets, I assure
you they would be spinning right now!
Focus!
Let's put that fire out!
Good. Again.
More arrows.
You heard Barrel, Joscar.
More arrows for fire, Pascar!
You two cut it out! That's enough!
You okay?
Hey, are you alright?
Wee-hee-hee.
We're going to storm the ship.
Is everyone ready?
Rawr! Rawr! Rawr!
Damn you!
Aaaaaah!
Nami! Go!
Break the mirrors! Hurry! But...
They're sending an army to attack you!
I can't stop them!
I'm too busy!
It'll take all I've got to
beat the guy I'm fighting!
Hey!
This looks bad!
It's too close!
We can't escape!
Are you there?
Luffy, I'm sorry.
I've got you now.
Tommy, what's wrong?
I think this might be it for us.